Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Reagan Books, 1968-1988 (Box 1-133)
  - 699-002-164. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, December 8, 1987 - December 12, 1987 (Box 93)
  - 699-002-164. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, December 8, 1987 - December 12, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-164. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, December 8, 1987 - December 12, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-166. RNC: Flash Results, January 27, 1988 - January 30, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-166. RNC: Flash Results, January 27, 1988 - January 30, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-166. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1988 - January 30, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-166. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1988 - January 30, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-166. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1988 - January 30, 1987 (Box 94)
  - 699-002-168. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 4, 1988 - April 7, 1988 (Box 95)
  - 699-002-168. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 4, 1988 - April 7, 1988 (Box 95)
  - 699-002-168. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 4, 1988 - April 7, 1988 (Box 95)
  - 699-002-168. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 4, 1988 - April 7, 1988 (Box 95)
  - 699-002-168. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 4, 1988 - April 7, 1988 (Box 95)
  - 699-002-168. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, April 4, 1988 - April 7, 1988 (Box 95)
  - 699-002-169. RNC: May Quorum, May 11, 1988 - May 14, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-169. RNC: May Quorum, May 11, 1988 - May 14, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-170. RNC: Flash Results, May 12, 1988 - May 15, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-170. RNC: Flash Results, May 12, 1988 - May 15, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-170. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, May 12, 1988 - May 15, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-170. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, May 12, 1988 - May 15, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-170. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, May 12, 1988 - May 15, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-170. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, May 12, 1988 - May 15, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-171. RNC: Flash Results, May 30, 1988 - May 31, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-171. RNC: Flash Results, May 30, 1988 - May 31, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-171. RNC: Flash Results, May 30, 1988 - May 31, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-171. RNC: Flash Results, May 30, 1988 - May 31, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-171. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes - 'Post Summit Tracking, May 30, 1988 - May 31, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-172. RNC: Flash Results, June 10, 1988 - June 12, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-172. RNC: Flash Results, June 10, 1988 - June 12, 1988 (Box 96)
  - 699-002-172. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, June 10, 1988 - June 12, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-172. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, June 10, 1988 - June 12, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-173. RNC: Flash Results, July 28, 1988 - July 30, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-173. RNC: Flash Results, July 28, 1988 - July 30, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-173. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, July 28, 1988 - July 30, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-173. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes - 'July National, July 28, 1988 - July 30, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-174. RNC: A Banner Report Based on Merged 1988 Data, January 1, 1988 - June 30, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-174. RNC: A Banner Report Based on Merged 1988 Data, January 1, 1988 - June 30, 1988 (Box 97)
  - 699-002-175. RNC: Flash Results, August 27, 1988 - August 28, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-175. RNC: Flash Results, August 27, 1988 - August 28, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-175. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, August 27, 1988 - August 28, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-175. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, August 27, 1988 - August 28, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-175. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, August 27, 1988 - August 28, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-176. RNC: Flash Results, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-176. RNC: Flash Results, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-176. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-176. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 98)
  - 699-002-176. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-176. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-177. RNC: Flash Results, November 1, 1988 - November 2, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-177. RNC: Pre-Election, November 1, 1988 - November 2, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-177. RNC: Pre-Election, November 1, 1988 - November 2, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-177. RNC: Pre-Election, November 1, 1988 - November 2, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Flash Results, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Flash Results, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Flash Results, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 99)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 100)
  - 699-002-178. RNC: Post Election, November 12, 1988 - November 17, 1988 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-180. RNC: State of The Union Message, February 4, 1986 - February 4, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-180. RNC: State of The Union Message, February 4, 1986 - February 4, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-181. RNC: Peace and National Security Address, February 26, 1986 - February 26, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-181. RNC: Peace and National Security Address, February 26, 1986 - February 26, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-181. RNC: Peace and National Security Address - 'Reagan Defense Speech, February 26, 1986 - February 26, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-182. RNC: Anti-Drug Crusade: Attitudes and Opportunities for Change, September 25, 1986 - September 25, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-182. RNC: Anti-Drug Crusade: Attitudes and Opportunities for Change, September 25, 1986 - September 25, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Flash Results, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Flash Results, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Flash Results, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 101)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-183. RNC: Iran Trax - November, November 17, 1986 - November 24, 1986 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-185. RNC: State of the Union Speech Analysis, January 27, 1987 - January 27, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-185. RNC: State of the Union Speech Analysis, January 27, 1987 - January 27, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-185. RNC: State of the Union Speech Analysis, January 27, 1987 - January 27, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-186. RNC: President Reagan's Address on The Venice Summit and Budget Issues, June 15, 1987 - July 15, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-186. RNC: President Reagan's Address on The Venice Summit and Budget Issues, June 15, 1987 - July 15, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-186. RNC: President Reagan's Address on The Venice Summit and Budget Issues, June 15, 1987 - July 15, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-187. RNC: Communication Focus Groups in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, October 5, 1987 - October 5, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-188. RNC: Presidential Address on the INF Summit, December 10, 1987 - December 10, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-188. RNC: Presidential Address on the INF Summit, December 10, 1987 - December 10, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-188. RNC: Presidential Address on the INF Summit, December 10, 1987 - December 10, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-189. RNC: 1988 State of The Union Address, January 25, 1988 - January 25, 1988 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-189. RNC: 1988 State of The Union Address, January 25, 1988 - January 25, 1988 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-189. RNC: 1988 State of The Union Address, January 25, 1988 - January 25, 1988 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-191. RNC: President Reagan's convention Address and Welcome Rally Speech, September 1, 1988 - September 1, 1988 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-194. RNC: National Merge (with breakout volumes), January 5, 1987 - August 2, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-194. RNC: National Merge (with breakout volumes), January 5, 1987 - August 2, 1987 (Box 102)
  - 699-002-205. RNC: Flash Results, January 6, 1984 - January 6, 1984 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-205. RNC: RNC `83, January 6, 1984 - January 6, 1984 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-205. RNC: RNC `83, January 6, 1984 - January 6, 1984 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-205. RNC: RNC `83, January 6, 1984 - January 6, 1984 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-205. RNC: RNC `83, January 6, 1984 - January 6, 1984 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-211. RNC: August Quorum 1988, August 9, 1988 - August 11, 1988 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-211. RNC: August Quorum 1988, August 9, 1988 - August 11, 1988 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-211. RNC: August Quorum 1988, August 9, 1988 - August 11, 1988 (Box 103)
  - 699-002-211. RNC: August Quorum 1988, August 9, 1988 - August 11, 1988 (Box 103)
  - 699-003-001. CFRP: Five State Survey, February 1, 1972 (Box 103)
  - 699-003-001. Nixon: Campaign Codes, Q'aire, Tab Specs., 1972? (Box 103)
  - 699-006-001.: A Survey of Attitudes Toward Private Enterprise, March 1, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-006-001.: A Survey of Attitudes Toward the American Party System, March 1, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-007-001. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate, September 2, 1975 - September 12, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-007-001. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate, September 2, 1975 - September 12, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-007-001. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate, September 2, 1975 - September 12, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-007-001. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate, September 2, 1975 - September 12, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-007-001. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate, September 2, 1975 - September 12, 1975 (Box 104)
  - 699-007-002. Citizens for Reagan: A National Panel Survey of the American Electorate, December 14, 1975 - December 14, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-002. Citizens for Reagan: A National Panel Survey of the American Electorate, December 14, 1975 - December 14, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-002. Citizens for Reagan: A National Panel Survey of the American Electorate, December 14, 1975 - December 14, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-002. Citizens for Reagan: A National Panel Survey of the American Electorate, December 14, 1975 - December 14, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-002. Citizens for Reagan: A National Panel Survey of the American Electorate, December 14, 1975 - December 14, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-003. Citizens for Reagan: A Focus Group Assessment of Seven Campaign Media Concepts, December 11, 1975 - December 13, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-003. Citizens for Reagan: A Focus Group Assessment of Seven Campaign Media Concepts, December 11, 1975 - December 13, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-003. Citizens for Reagan: A Focus Group Assessment of Seven Campaign Media Concepts, December 11, 1975 - December 13, 1975 (Box 105)
  - 699-007-003. Citizens for Reagan: A Focus Group Assessment of Seven Campaign Media Concepts, December 11, 1975 - December 13, 1975 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-003. Citizens for Reagan: A Focus Group Assessment of Seven Campaign Media Concepts, December 11, 1975 - December 13, 1975 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 106)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 107)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 107)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 107)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 107)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 107)
  - 699-007-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate (Post-Primary), June 17, 1976 - June 28, 1976 (Box 107)
  - 699-007-008. Citizens for Reagan: Listening Post: The first 4 weeks, January 22, 1976 - February 18, 1976 (Box 108)
  - 699-007-009. Citizens for Reagan: A Survey of Republican Voters in the State of Illinois, December 1, 1975 (Box 108)
  - 699-007-021. Citizens for Reagan: Third Survey of Republican Voters in New Hampshire, February 1, 1976 (Box 108)
  - 699-011-001. Citizens for the Republic: National Post Election 1976 (Box 108)
  - 699-011-001. Citizens for the Republic: National Post Election 1976 (Box 108)
  - 699-011-001. Citizens for the Republic: National Post Election 1976 (Box 108)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-001. Reagan for President: National Survey of Voter Attitides, March 24, 1979 - April 7, 1979 (Box 109)
  - 699-016-002. Reagan for President Committee: Voter Values and Attitudes, June 1, 1979 - June 8, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-002. Reagan for President Committee: Voter Values and Attitudes, June 1, 1979 - June 8, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-002. Reagan for President Committee: Voter Values and Attitudes, June 1, 1979 - June 8, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-002. Reagan for President Committee: Voter Values and Attitudes, June 1, 1979 - June 8, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-003. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Survey Focusing on Attitudes Towards A North American Announcement Themes, September 13, 1979 - September 16, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-003. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Survey Focusing on Attitudes Towards A North American Announcement Themes, September 13, 1979 - September 16, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-003. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Survey Focusing on Attitudes Towards A North American Announcement Themes, September 13, 1979 - September 16, 1979 (Box 110)
  - 699-016-003. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Survey Focusing on Attitudes Towards A North American Announcement Themes, September 13, 1979 - September 16, 1979 (Box 111)
  - 699-016-003. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Survey Focusing on Attitudes Towards A North American Announcement Themes, September 13, 1979 - September 16, 1979 (Box 111)
  - 699-016-004. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Panel Survey, November 21, 1979 - November 27, 1979 (Box 111)
  - 699-016-004. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Panel Survey, November 21, 1979 - November 27, 1979 (Box 111)
  - 699-016-004. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Panel Survey, November 21, 1979 - November 27, 1979 (Box 111)
  - 699-016-004. Reagan for President: A Nationwide Panel Survey, November 21, 1979 - November 27, 1979 (Box 112)
  - 699-016-005. Reagan for President: Panel Survey of Voters Values and Attitudes in 12 major US Urban Areas, December 13, 1979 - December 18, 1979 (Box 112)
  - 699-016-005. Reagan for President: Panel Survey of Voters Values and Attitudes in 12 major US Urban Areas, December 13, 1979 - December 18, 1979 (Box 112)
  - 699-016-006. Reagan for President: National Telephone Survey of Voters, March 28, 1980 - April 7, 1980 (Box 112)
  - 699-016-006. Reagan for President: National Telephone Survey of Voters, March 28, 1980 - April 7, 1980 (Box 112)
  - 699-016-006. Reagan for President: National Telephone Survey of Voters, March 28, 1980 - April 7, 1980 (Box 113)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 113)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 113)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 113)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 113)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 113)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-007. Reagan for President: Voter Attitudes toward Vice Presidential Attributes and the Potential Nominees, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-008. Reagan/Bush: Campaign Plan, June 29, 1980 - June 29, 1980 (Box 114)
  - 699-016-009. Reagan/Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes- Run II, July 23, 1980 - July 25, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-010. Reagan/Bush Committee: Special Computer Run from Two National Surveys #7381 & 7861, June 1, 1980 - July 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-010. Reagan/Bush Committee: Special Computer Run from Two National Surveys #7381 & 7861, June 1, 1980 - July 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-010. Reagan/Bush Committee: Special Computer Run from Two National Surveys #7381 & 7861, June 1, 1980 - July 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-010. Reagan/Bush Committee: Special Computer Run from Two National Surveys #7381 & 7861, June 1, 1980 - July 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-010. Reagan/Bush Committee: Special Computer Run from Two National Surveys #7381 & 7861, June 1, 1980 - July 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-011. Reagan/Bush: National Survey Wave I, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-011. Reagan/Bush: National Survey Wave I, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-011. Reagan/Bush: National Survey Wave I, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 115)
  - 699-016-011. Reagan/Bush: National Survey Wave I, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-011. Reagan/Bush: National Survey Wave I, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 116)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 117)
  - 699-016-012. Reagan-Bush Committee: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 117)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 117)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 117)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 117)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 117)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 118)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 118)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 118)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 118)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 118)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 118)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 119)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 119)
  - 699-016-013. RNC: A National Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes, September 27, 1980 - September 30, 1980 (Box 119)